Welcome back.
欢迎回来。
In this video, we would talk about one of the new features in Java 5, which is called Auto Boxing, which
在这段视频中，我们将讨论Java 5中的一个新功能，它被称为自动装箱，这
allows you to write code with primitive values, but compiler does a lot of work for you and converts
它允许你用原始值编写代码，但编译器会帮你做很多工作，并将它们转换成
them into wrappers.
它们转化为包装器。
And also, we would look at a few constants that are defined inside these wrapper classes.
还有，我们会看一下这些包装器类里面定义的一些常量。
Let's get started with this concept called Auto Boxing.
让我们从这个叫做自动装箱的概念开始。
So, I said the way you would create a wrapper class is by saying Integer seven = Integer.valueOf(7)
所以，我说过，你创建一个包装器类的方法是：Integer seven = Integer.valueOf(7)
,
right.
对。
So, this is the way
所以，这就是
we were creating wrapper classes until now.
我们直到现在还在创建封装类。
But this is too long a way because you can do this as well.
但这种方式太长了，因为你也可以这样做。
What is happening in here is Auto Boxing.
这里所发生的是自动装箱。
What happens is when you do this, Java in the background would do this, Integer.valueOf(7) and create
发生的情况是，当你这样做的时候，Java在后台会这样做，Integer.valueOf(7)并创建一个实例。
an instance of it and put the reference of it in seven.
它的一个实例，并把它的引用放在7里面。
This feature in Java is called Auto boxing.
这个功能在Java中被称为自动装箱。
The important thing is Auto Boxing uses Integer.valueOf
重要的是，自动装箱使用Integer.valueOf
and we know that Integer.valueOf uses all the things again.
而我们知道，Integer.valueOf又使用了所有的东西。
So, if I create something like sevenAgain and = 7, because these are using Integer.valueOf,
所以，如果我创建像sevenAgain和=7这样的东西，因为这些是使用Integer.valueOf。
you would see that these are referring to the same variable. So, if I say seven == sevenAgain,
你会发现，这些都是指同一个变量。所以，如果我说seven == sevenAgain,
you would see that the value is true. Auto Boxing uses Integer.valueOf. The existing objects,
你会看到这个值是真的。Auto Boxing使用Integer.valueOf。现有的对象。
the existing wrapper class objects are reused and you can see that the same reference is present in both
现有的封装类对象被重用，你可以看到相同的引用同时存在于
seven and sevenAgain. Auto Boxing is a very important thing. At later stage, we would also look at how do we use
seven和sevenAgain中。自动装箱是一件非常重要的事情。在后面的阶段，我们还将研究如何使用
Auto Boxing to add primitive values to a collection. Features like this are called syntactic sugar,
自动框定来向集合中添加原始值。像这样的功能被称为语法糖。
right.
对。
Who wants to type in the extra characters?
谁愿意输入额外的字符呢？
I'm a lazy guy
我是一个懒惰的人
and so I guess, would be you.
所以我猜你也是。
So, we don't really want to type in a lot of code and that's where features like Auto Boxing would really
所以，我们并不真的想输入大量的代码，这就是像自动装箱这样的功能真正的帮助。
help.
帮助。
Having looked at all these features on the wrapper classes, the last thing which we want to talk about wrapper
在看了所有这些关于包装器类的特性之后，我们想谈的最后一件事是包装器
classes is the different constants, which are defined on each of these wrapper classes.
类的最后一点是不同的常量，这些常量被定义在每个包装器类上。
So, if you look at the wrapper classes, they have a MAX_VALUE.
所以，如果你看一下包装器类，它们有一个MAX_VALUE。
It indicates what max value can a integer hold.
它表示一个整数能容纳的最大值。
They also have a MIN_VALUE; what is the minimum value that an integer can hold. If you want to find the
它们也有一个MIN_VALUE；什么是一个整数能容纳的最小值。如果你想找到
size of an integer,
一个整数的大小。
you can do that as well and you can get the size in bytes as well. So, size is in bits.
你也可以这样做，你也可以得到字节的大小。所以，大小的单位是比特。
So, this is 32 bits and this is 4 bytes. These kind of constants are present on all the wrapper classes.
所以，这是32位，这是4字节。这些常量存在于所有的封装类中。
In this video and the previous sets of videos, we looked at wrapper classes, we looked at the fact that
在这段视频和之前的几段视频中，我们看了包装类，我们看了它们是不可变的这一事实。
they're immutable, we looked at the fact that there are a wide variety of features that these wrapper
它们是不可变的，我们看了这些包装类提供的各种功能的事实
classes offer, and we looked at the fact that we should always use valueOf instead of using new with
类所提供的各种功能，以及我们应该始终使用valueOf而不是使用new的事实。
the wrapper classes. We also looked at the various constants that are present in this wrapper class like
而不是使用new。我们还研究了这个封装类中存在的各种常量，如
MAX_VALUE, MIN_VALUE, SIZE, and BYTES which would help us get more information about what kind of values
MAX_VALUE、MIN_VALUE、SIZE和BOTTES，这将帮助我们获得更多关于在这些包装类中可以存储哪些值的信息。
you can store into these wrapper classes.
你可以在这些封装类中存储什么样的值。
I'll see you in the next video where we would start discussing about a brand new topic.
我们将在下一个视频中见，届时我们将开始讨论一个全新的话题。
Until then, bye bye.
在那之前，再见了。